<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>supamakoto</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/</link>
    <description>Recent content on supamakoto</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>de</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Erste Sonne 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/posts/erste-sonne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/posts/erste-sonne/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/img/erste-sonne.webp&#34; alt=&#34;Beschreibung&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Direkt die erste Sonne 2026 für einen kleinen Fahrradausflug mit der Jüngsten genutzt. So schön.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zahnspange</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/posts/zahnspange/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/posts/zahnspange/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Die Große kriegt heute ihre Zangspange. Wie die Zeit vergeht. Gestern noch mit dem Rollschaf durch die Wohnung gedonnert. Heute Zahnspange und danach fünf Stunden YouTube gucken zum Entspannen. It is what it is till it ain&amp;rsquo;t. Festhalten geht nicht. Die Momente bewusst wahrnehmen hingegen schon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cr1TiKaL zu Section 230</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/quote/mein-erster-quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/quote/mein-erster-quote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It should be obvious why section 230 is so important because if these platforms were held liable for every single thing people post on their platforms, they would get into a lot of hot water and they would just not allow people to post things. Full stop. because it would be too dangerous to do so. They would need to micromanage and control every single thing that hits the platform in order to protect themselves. No matter how you spin it, this would ruin the internet. It’s a pile of dogshit. No matter how much perfume gets sprayed on it or how they want to repackage it, it still stinks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die with zero</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/quote/die-with-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/quote/die-with-zero/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’d rather spend my time and energy trying to live the most fulfilling life I can than to accumulate a sum of money. Money itself doesn’t build relationships, create memories, bring you closer to your loved ones, or express who you are to the world. It’s how you spend money that can make those things easier. When you optimize for net fulfillment over net worth, it’s a whole different game. It shifted my “save to make number go up” mindset to a different frame: “spend what we are able to on the things that matter most.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Studie: Amerikaner und ihr Verhältnis zu Nachrichten</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/quote/pew-usa-news-medienwandel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/quote/pew-usa-news-medienwandel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Two-thirds say they have stopped getting news from a specific source, and six-in-ten say they have reduced their overall news intake.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Link: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pewresearch.org/journalism/2026/02/11/americans-complicated-relationship-with-news/&#34;&gt;Pew Research Center&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to blogging</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/posts/mein-erster-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/posts/mein-erster-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/img/mf.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Beschreibung&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Alles auf Anfang. Endlich wieder bloggen. Lange ist es her. Viel zu lange. Wenn man mit seinem Blog Geld verdient, macht man zwar sein Hobby zum Beruf, aber man verliert auch sein Hobby. Diese kleine Ecke des World Wide Web gehört einfach nur mir. Links, Zitate, Fotos aus meinem Alltag, Tools, die ich nutze, Dinge, die mich inspirieren. Alles super easy mit Hugo aufgesetzt und per Github ins Netz gestellt. Am HTML und CSS basteln, mit Terminal auseinandersetzen. Was für eine Freude.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study of Buddhist Monks Finds Meditation Alters Brain Activity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/link/mein-erster-post-kopie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/link/mein-erster-post-kopie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Meditation isn’t thinking about nothing. New research reinforces that it’s a mind-altering, dynamic state that promotes focus, learning, and well-being.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Über</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/ueber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/supamakoto/ueber/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Moin, willkommen auf meinem persönlichen Blog. Hier halte ich fest, was mich interessiert und inspiriert. No pressure. Einfach bloggen. Ohne Tracking, ohne Likes, ohne Hintergedanken. Wenn dir etwas gefällt, schön. Falls nicht, auch okay. Es geht hier nicht darum, Sichtbarkeit zu schaffen. Für mich ist diese Seite einfach nur mein ganz persönlicher Space in diesem World Wide Web. Mit Markdown geschrieben, über Hugo ins Netz gehoben, per GitHub veröffentlicht. Keine Skripte, keine Like-Buttons, keine Box für ein E-Mail-Sign-up. Nur RSS, HTML, CSS, jede Menge Drum and Bass, Kaffee und Freude am Bloggen. &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:supamakoto@mailbox.org&#34;&gt;Say hi!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
